[Music]
hello and welcome to our busy Central
lunch event about uh 2024 release wave 1
this time we want to present one local
uh functionality fun set of
functionalities and it will be related
what is new uh about Danish bookkeeping
act we already deliver U the same uh
topic previous wave but previous wave
was before final um development from our
side the final decision from uh DBA so
we wanted to update what is really new
what is the most important so this is
mostly about updated features and the
most important you need to take care uh
my name is to I'm product manager and I
was responsible from about this set of
functionality and together with me is
ell soft engineer who made a lot of
great functionality related with Danish
bookkeeping act so agenda will not be
complicated we will pass through
introduction and scope some timeline
when we started how we started what we
deliver and when and we will go
straightforward to new features why and
how Okay um new new Danish bookkeeping
act has has been announced
2022 um what is important business
Central is certified in Denmark by DBA
in first phase in the first set from
January 1st 2024 so we are fully
certified you can find on this link full
list of all certified Solutions uh when
they are certified who is certified who
is not so we are certified but let's
explain what is certify uh Microsoft
certify as a standard solution that
means uh as is because we cannot predict
what can be extended so by DBA this is
registered as standard solution and only
as a cloud
option um we will talk what is not a
standard solution not standard solution
is um if you change some Behavior
required by the DBA doesn't mean that
every customization will be uh outside
of standard solution but everything what
is related with bookkeeping with the
keeping uh data for 5 years for example
it will not be standard solution uh
anymore so uh you are responsible for
your customizations um you need to to
see if this customizations uh
customizations have an impact on a
standard solution and to make decision
uh and to check the DBA eventually if
you need to certify your solution as
this is highly customized or this is
still uh available as a standard
Solution by based by Microsoft if you're
an isv and if your isv solution has any
impact on this area
what I mentioned yeah you definitely
need to certify your solution you can
certify your isv name to together a busy
Central and that's okay and um when you
start to certify you can ask from DBA
documentation Microsoft uh use so you
can reuse some of these documentation
not everything but more than 90% of
documentation are available publicly so
you can reuse it um and if you're using
on print solution we didn't certify on
print solution currently this is not
possible because of some um physical
limitation so you must certify your on
Prem Solution by yourself it doesn't
mean that all these features will not be
available in on Prem the most of them
that means almost everything what we
will show today I will mention what is
not available in on Prem solution you
can reuse in your own PR solution so
this is let's say already for
certification but you need to finish few
things and to certify by
yourself when we started we were really
dedicated to provide full compliance to
all our customers uh we wanted to
provide uh in a first available way we
wanted to have you secured that we are
on a right PA and we want to have
certified solution for you we
communicated everywhere on a BC we even
had our promising on our Doc Page for
Denmark local environment so we did it
and we were focused and we mentioned
from the beginning that we were focused
on Cloud solution we started immediately
design and redesign uh as soon as we go
as we got information what we need to do
final information sometimes we had just
better instruction and we didn't want to
start with something we need to change
lately even we had to do with in in a
few cases but what we try to do more uh
everything what we could see if we can
be applicable in more countries or maybe
in the future uh can be applicable more
countries we deliver this as a W1 Bas
app or as a global apps only what is
really local be kept as a local features
and um we require you know all these
features finished we certified and now
what we will continue we will continue
process of improvements so some things
maybe are not perfect so now we are
listening your feedback but keep in mind
that all your feedback um we first need
to filter it because we are enforced by
the law we must be compliant by the law
and if there is some space we can make
more um better options and better user
experience for you in uh borders of this
law we will do it so uh new Danish
bookkeeping act as said announced in
2022 uh Microsoft and um decided to go
uh together with common collaboration of
busy Central and finance operation team
Finance team so both of teams started to
research all necessary information
together so we didn't want to to go
separately and then to make different
ideas so ideas and S Solutions can be
different because different architecture
or to different solutions but everything
what we could do we try to do with some
uh common decisions then somewhere in
the beginning of um 2023 we created our
business Central backlog what we will do
and immediately after making this
backlog we
created spec specific uh channel on
Yammer for Danish bookkeeping act so we
started to communicate communicate with
partners and uh soon after that we
created our first virtual machine uh and
published on Yammer it was if I'm not
wrong now I'm trying to recall it was
about sft so you could start with early
testing this is and this was our idea
and this is and it will be in the future
to be as more transparent as possible
every time when it is
possible uh then on a previous launch
event they said we presented this topic
then on the Rea we had a
um communication with many of Danish
Partners there to explain what is there
and then we finish pre-registration uh
Pro Finish we submitted uh our
documentation for pre-registrations it
was open so we wanted to be the first
and we had let's say approximately 90%
of finished job we submitted to uh to uh
pre-registration process so we wanted to
get early feedback from DBA to see what
we need to change some final
registration documentation submitted
after few changes in a me me time and
yes officially B Central uh was certifi
on the January from January 1st this
year
now uh few days actually month after
that yes from February 1st uh we updated
our terms of use for uh Denmark so now
we have we are abolutely compliance we
didn't activate the skipping 5 years
before we updated our documentation so
now we are absolutely compliant and we
are starting after more more than 300
engineering days in Investments on
building all these features now we are
starting with a new phase Improvement
based on feedback so we will first wait
to collect some feedbacks to see what we
can do and all this information and all
this requirements we we are getting from
you every day or let's say every week uh
we will collect and we will first
discuss with DBA because we must check
with them if we can apply L these ideas
and when we get positive answer from DBA
we will improve this functionality for
sure
what we have uh as a functionality just
high level we have export to sft uh we
have public standard chart of account
and V chart of account we can now upload
CSP file um uh with accounting data to
Reg basis uh e submission of V
registration notification with name
handle um um yes name handle registered
and electronic invoicing uh then
mandatory digital vouchers as
attachments and keeping your data for 5
years the data compliance so now let's
go step by step first I will shortly
explain about sft and then Arthur will
show you uh more details you will see
sft is in title but there are much more
features sft is app but in this app uh F
yeah first this app was built on the top
of AIT file export standard global app
this is something what we deliver from
uh uh broad market and now on top of
that we are just using different formats
for different countries sft is enabl in
Denmark and this feature is
pre-installed of course in in your
environments your localizations what is
there inside inside this app you can
find public start standard chart of
account public standard V chart of
account standard audit file export and
this is based on DK format actually this
is Standard Export but a few Fields um
added and uh we have import as a file to
keep the history so you can export this
is full functionality for export
but uh we were required to have
opportunity to offer you to import sft
so you can import SF file and keep this
as a history and U using the same audit
file export app we added export
bookkeeping data to regas basis as a CSV
file because this is really great based
on performances you can export in your
active session you can export later if
you have millions of Entry so this is
really good app I'm talk about OD file
export and we reuse for for any type of
export every time when we can so now I
will give a screen to Arthur to show you
public start standard chart of account
sft and regasa basis expert to CSV
Arthur the sft feature is available uh
from the feature management so once you
enable the feature in one company it
will be enabled for all the other
companies um so if you want to set this
feature up for other companies you can
type in Search sft and you can open the
sft setup guide uh on the first step of
this guide uh there will be explained
what the feature going to do and on the
next one you can uh choose the standard
account type uh that will be for digit
standard account when you choose this
one and go next the next step step will
be to identify the uh reporting period
for the uh sft you can choose uh from
the accounting period table let me
choose 2026 and once I select this uh
you can notice the starting and ending
date are populated and the accounting
period type is accounting period you can
also see that there is an action that is
called create CH chart of accounts so if
you don't have the chart accounts uh uh
in your uh installation you can create
it based on the standard uh chart of
accounts
uh next I want to do the mapping between
my chart of accounts because I do have
it and the standard standard chart of
accounts uh there is an action that
could help me to do this it's called
much match chart of accounts and let me
show you how does it work so if I click
this one and if I
confirm I can see that 57 of 18600
accounts automatically matched and how I
can check this I can click open the
setup page
and I can notice that some of those
accounts been matched and those are
exact those are exactly identical
accounts so for example you can see uh
this one and this one they are matched
uh where you can find the standard
accounts are exactly this so on this uh
sub page you can notice on the left side
g account number this is your chart of
accounts uh accounts and on the right
side you can notice a standard accounts
number
and if I look up to this one you can see
the list of all the public standard
accounts uh that you need to use and the
rule for the saf you need to do the
mapping for all the charts of for all
the accounts in your chart uh for the
testing purpose I want to do this in the
header in the header I have the field
standard account number I want to choose
a single account here and update for all
accounts of course this is something
that that you don't want to do you want
to specify a very specific standard
account per each of your accounts but
for the sake of presentation I want to
do
this uh and then I can see that all DL
accounts
mapped The Next Step will be the mapping
of the VT posting setup uh for every
single VT posting setup I can specify
the uh VT code either sales VT reporting
or the purchase VT reporting code
depends on what you choose and I can
look up to this one and here I can find
all the VT reporting
codes uh but that's optional you don't
need to do
this uh the next one will be export
dation Dimensions to the saf you can
notice that we automatically set the
specific analysis type code for every
single Dimension and you can notice that
there is an option that is called SF
expert so if you don't want to expert a
certain Dimension you can uh remove the
check from this
field and the last one uh will be to
specify the employee so the information
from that employee will be part of the
sft file let me choose the employee and
the setup is completed uh and that step
the next one will be the generation of
the SF file um itself for that I want to
open the audit File Expert documents and
I want to create a new document
uh and then the header I need to choose
the sft file format I want to choose my
GL account mapping for this period
2026 as you can see the dates are
prepopulated and you can notice uh a
wide range of different options I'm not
going to cover all of them unless uh the
one on the processing TP the option is
called parallel processing and that will
help you to schedule the generation of
thef file to this for example hours
because as you can imagine this is audit
file uh we're going to export all the
general energy entries for single year
so that will take a lot of time with
this option you can schedule this to the
appropriate uh time uh I want to do this
because I don't have a lot of data so I
will unle this one and I want to start
the generation of the safy file I want
to click Start
action uh confirm that okay I want to
start the new generation right now
uh and then when the duration is
completed let me check let me show you
what we have right now on the line sub
form we have three types of data we have
Master data we have general ledger
entries for January this is the only
months when I have posted data and the
source
documents uh and let's see how it
reflects on the uh files itself I want
to click download files and I will have
a single Z archive uh let me download
this one and inside of
this archive file let me show you uh we
have exactly three files the first one
master data the second one general
ledger entries and the third one source
documents exactly what you see on the
lines sub page that is it with the saf
file generation and the other important
part of the SF app uh in scope of this
app we also provide you the generation
of the file the scope uh raincap basis
for that you need to search for RB un
counting
file you need to choose the mapping
header absolutely the same like in the
saf
file uh you will have the dates right
here starting ending dates and here you
have two options for calculation of the
balance both for income statement and
for the balance account you can choose
either net change or the balance at date
for this one and for this one as well
and of course we uh provide you some
default values and then you need to
click click generate file and the file
will be generated uh let's quickly check
what we have in this
file and this file that is Syle CSV file
when we have the data about every single
account the name of account uh and the
balance depends on your setup and that
includes my demo back to you
Alexander thank you Arthur for your demo
and now let's move to the next topic
next topic is V is submission so now you
must electronically submit your v in
Denmark and that means the bookkeeping
system standard bookkeeping system must
support reporting of v v Danish tax
Authority V API uh busy Central now
supports V submission through tax API to
scut uh this app is already finished it
does not require customer certificate
this is important because Microsoft has
built in uh inside and yeah it was uh in
one moment they said some we didn't have
clear requirements and we first created
uh new functionality where you can where
you had to use your own certificate but
on the end uh this requirement was uh
let's say make more clear to use proper
expressions and we were en forced to use
Microsoft certificate for all our Cloud
customers so we updated we made some
changes there so currently documentation
maybe is not um fully uh uh changed it
will be updated in the next few days so
uh what you have there you have this
feature pre-installed by default cloud
and on Prem but certificate Microsoft
certificate is preinstalled only the
Cloud solution for on print solution you
must use your own certificate so you
need to ask from Scot and to use the
certificate certificate for on print
solutions next one is n handle
notification and registration
uh this is something what um yeah we had
a lot of discussion with many partners
with enforc notification but this is by
the law so
um when you create a company you will
get uh notification if your company to
get you need to popul CVR number and if
you do not have CV number or if your uh
CV number is not register Vietnam handle
you will get this maybe annoying
notification but this is something what
is must and you will get there you can
uh switch off uh this notification in
sandbox environment but you cannot do it
in production in production you do not
have actually this is not a blocker you
just need to to see it and if you want
to uh for you to disappear this
notification you must go to name Handler
register you will have instruction in
this notification go there register your
company from that moment this
notification will disappear API will
automatically check from the moment when
you register there this notification
will not exist anymore this u n hand
registration is not only for this
notification it will be necessary for
your invoicing in the future so this is
not blocker uh technically this is not a
blocker maybe just a no notification but
you must have this registration with
handle if you want to work with some
other
features so next I just mentioned
invoicing based we created invoicing
this is based on global e document
framework we enable both formats obl and
pep so you can choose choose whatever
you want when you open a document
service and you create new service you
can choose service for ubl or pay or you
can create both of services and decide
for based on your uh customer vendors
which service you want to use uh this is
support for delivering receiving
invoices so you can use sales process
but you can all also use in receiving
invoices from your vendor so it works in
both the directions it works with the
messages uh approving rejecting statuses
you can find in logs about every e
document so this is uh everything
actually what is required by the law and
probably much more
currently uh we have full document
exchange as I said messaging in this
moment we have enable only one uh
service but we are we are looking to
enable more services by default and we
are open for other apps so we had this
one as a more the most proactive who
work for the beginning but we want to
enable as soon as possible more services
by default inside the bus Central um uh
yes and yeah what I wanted to mention
important we do not provide direct
connection with n handle for direct
connection with n handle Danish
authorities required to have n handle
certified service so Microsoft is not in
a business of uh invoicing and we do not
have uh certified service so this is the
reason why you need to use some of
certifi access points this is not
possible to directly connect with name
handle if you're not uh certified
service so you must use some of existing
default we have uh in our app or some
other
app and next topic and this topic we'll
have a demo as well so I will not talk
so much mandatory digital vouchers this
feature is enabled as a global feature
uh globally this is voluntary so you can
say voluntary voluntary for
administrators and partners so you can
choose if you want use or do not but if
you decide to use this feature will
enforce users to attach some mandatory
digital vouchers or attachments whatever
we call this to uh some specific uh
documents in sales purchase general
journal s Journal purchase journals
combination with different Source codes
so for example you can use general
journal if you choose Source codes for
payroll so you will be enforced only if
you have pay source code on general
journal for other General journals it
will not be enforced so you can set up
as you one but in Denmark it will be by
default currently this is still
voluntary until July 1st from July 1st
it will be enforced so from that moment
you will be enforced to use mandatory
digital vouchers in sales and purchase
documents for other types of documents
you can choose if you want but for these
two types of documents you will be
enforced for purchase you must update
you must attach manually uh purchase a
document but for sales we have
automatically creation generation
actually document when you post sales
invoice syst will automatically create
and attach you can attach manual if you
want but we have this automation we try
to automate as more as
possible so
um this this feature as I said is start
July 1st and now I would like not to
talk more about that I think it would be
much better to see through demo so
Arthur please take your stage and show
us mandatory digital
vouchers the digital voucher feature is
available from the assistant
setup uh when I click setup digital
voucher feature the digital voucher
guide will be open the first step is an
explanation about the feature the next
one is the page where I can open the
important and uh um the the important
part of this setup it's called the
digital voucher entry setup and this is
exactly what Alexander shown on his
slide so here we have the setup for the
sales documents we have the attachment
it means that for every single Sal
documents there should be a digital
voucher attached uh but we have the
options generate automatically and it
means that if you do not uh attach the
document manual it will be automatically
generated and I will present this
scenario and the second one is purchase
document here we have the same check
type attachments but we do not offer
generation of automatically and the
important part is the enforcement
enforcement means that you won't be able
to change the check type so right now I
can change from attachment to no check
but from the 1 of July um won be able to
do
this uh then for the journal the
important part of the setup is called
the source code um so for example when I
set up for the sales Journal I can
specify all the source codes connected
to the journal when I click Source codes
I can see that the source code for this
one is the sales Journal it means that
when I post something from the journal
uh system will verify that we have the
source code sales journal and this setup
will be applied for this kind of of
journals let me show you the scenario I
will complete the setup and I will show
this scenario with the purchase invoice
first I want to create the new purchase
invoice specify the vendor invoice
number and then add something to the
lines
and at this point I don't want to attach
anything I want to check how the system
behave if I don't have any attachment
and I want to post the invoice and I
will see there message that it's not
possible to post without attaching the
digital voucher so let me attach the
digital voucher uh I can do this from
the incoming document files F box on the
right side I click incoming document
files and then the action is called
attach file file I want to choose my PDF
from the vendor and then I want to try
to post
again the document is
posted and let's see so we have the
incoming document file right here and
the most important part is that we have
the same incoming document file for all
uh the associated entries for example if
I go to general ledger entry
uh I can also find the incoming document
file for every single G
entry now let me show you the scenario
with the sales
invoice with the sales invoice I'm going
to do the very same steps so I want to
create a symbol sales
invoice and I don't want
to um attach any digital voucher and
that will be a little bit different from
the purchase invoice where I got the
error uh for the sales document uh in
according to the setup the document will
be generated automatically so when I
click I want to post invoice I can see
that the invoice is
posted and in the posted document and
also in the all the associated entries I
can see that there is incoming document
file attached let me download the file
and show you how does it look and this
is the the regular invoice uh in the
business Central so this is generated
automatically and attached to the posted
sales invoice as the digital voucher and
that concludes my demo back to you
Alexander okay thank you Arthur for
great demo before I continue I just want
to emphasize one more thing we didn't
mention um uh about that once when you
post document with attachment you cannot
remove this attachment after that you
cannot update but you can add additional
attachment so this is not a problem if
you have something else you forgot to
add maybe you had two three 10 different
uh documents you can attach them even if
document is posted but you cannot REM
remove original one or update original
one okay let's continue maybe to the
most complicated and yeah uh the most
weird situation about storage of the
faction and voucher for 5 years this is
first this first slid is about
requirements from DBA that means that we
must be as a service provider as a and
now just not forget everything what I'm
talking right now it is applicable only
for cloud this does not exist in a on
Prem solution for this is a problem we
cannot certify on Prem solution you need
to find you need to read the DB
requirements and to make some solution
for
you um storage transactions uh must
exist for all the cor transaction and
receipts or vouchers for minimum for
minimum for five years after the end of
financial years these uh transaction and
receipts must be stored this way that
company who made them they cannot change
uh back day delete whatever so they are
secure absolutely from any additional
interaction all transaction and vouchers
must be stored regardless of any
termination of your contract with
Microsoft so even if you stop to pay
subscription we must continue keep this
data even if customer go to bankruptcy
forcey solution whatever must keep from
the last uh fiscal year minimum for five
years this data and all encrypted
booking data must be decrypted into a
structure and machine readable format so
this is a this is this was a big
challenge this were the big challenges
with looking all these requirements and
we try to find the best solution for
that not to make over complicated for
implementation so right now you do not
need to do anything from your side what
we are doing busy Central export require
data on a daily basis to secure Asia Bob
uh blob storage we will um export
transaction data and digital
vouchers uh you cannot find this data
you do not have any access we do not
have access to this data uh they cannot
be changed back data or deleted by any
user uh everything what is more than 5
years old I say five plus years five
plus years after last fiscal year just
to be clear about that it it will be
automatically removed from our storage
so we will not keep this data forever
forever only the last five years after
your uh end of your fiscal year so we
have automated process for removing
because we want to behave uh related
with gdpr instructions and we can keep
only what is uh requ maximum what is
required by the Low by the low it is
required 5 years and we are doing only
this and this is updated in our terms of
use uh to start this
uh updating you must have your CVR
number in compan information without
that we cannot export um your data but
on the other side we had to prevent
non-exporting data because this is
required by the laow we must export your
data we must keep your data so we
blocked all General lged transactions if
you didn't enter your CVR number so you
must enter your CVR number in company
information if you want to use this
company for transactions so you can
create a company you can create for
example as a master data company no
problem you will not be enforced to use
c number if you don't have transactions
but if you want to have transactions you
must enter your CV number and C number
is not essential only for that this is
essential for sft for invoicing uh evat
for many other things and just to be
clear CVR number in Denmark is a
registered number in company information
let me say CV number we think on
register number in company
information and let's be more
transparent we want to be absolutely
transparent with you so this is set of
table what we will export you can see in
this second sentence actually this is
set of table but not all fields we are
exporting only minimal set of fields
required by the law actually required by
theba
so you will see uh transaction data GL
entry customer Ledger entry tell
customer vendor and so on so on you can
you can see on this um purple box then
in a light blue if I'm not wrong with
the colors you can see documents sales
invoice header sales invoice line credit
memo header lines purchase invoice
purchase credit memo header reminders
that all documents related with some
transactions will be here even post
general journal lines then in the right
side you have some additional
information Master data actually
currency currey ex change rates uh
general ledger account customer rendor
bank account fix ass set depreciation
book it fixes ass set depreciation book
because all of this information are
required so um theba can control if
something is wrong in uh uh other
transactions we cannot use this data we
do not have access there as you do not
have and only if uh official uh DBA
requirements comes to us to DBA or
prosecutor someone who has uh uh this
power to ask this data from Microsoft
Microsoft will deliver them as protected
so this is not something what we will do
uh intentionally for any other purpose
we are keeping this only for this
situation so if we are enforced by the
law but some agency from Denmark with
this power we will deliver this data to
them only one way and as there were many
misunderstanding about CIA number I
wanted to WRA up a bit more about CA
number what is about when you are
blocked when you are not
um Pro probably this is everything is uh
too complicated so I just wanted to Dr
up this again okay we have company
information and we are talking only a
production environment in sandbox
environment you can use without any
problem and I didn't mention uh as I
said in uh sandbox environment you can
um uh turn off this notification for
example from the moment you enter CV
number you cannot remove the CV number
in production company this is important
but if you copy production comp to new
one CVR number will not be copied so
everything will be copied except CVR
number in company information so you can
easily create copy of your company and
you will not be blocked so only your
production company for the moment
entering CV number it will be blocked so
if you want and you cannot delease this
company
anymore this is related for production
environment and company with a CVR
number now if you want to test don't do
this in production environment use
sandbox environment because you don't
have any problem to test to make any
test in a sandbox environment in
production you cannot because this is
required by the law now we have CVR
number there what if I didn't populate
CVR number company information you will
see notification that you are not
register with name handle this is not
blocker this is just annoying
notification
then um user cannot post to general
ledger this is not because of name
handle notification this is because you
are enforced to have CVA number so we
can export data for keeping for five
years so without CVR number you will get
a no notification but you do not this is
not now mandatory to be registered with
name handle you will be blocked because
you didn't enter CVA number now when you
enter CVA number but you are still not
register with name handle notification
will disappear that's okay you will not
have this notification anymore but and
uh sorry I just said wrong thing this
notification will see ex this because
you are not register vam handle but you
will be unblocked so you can continue uh
posting without any problem but you are
not registered and you will still have
this notification and now if you have
CVR number and you are registered with
them handle you of course you will not
be blocked because you already have CVR
number but notification will disappear
notification for n registration it will
disappear because now you have CV number
and you register with name handle no
problem production company as I
mentioned in the beginning cannot be
deleted and again just to emphasize if
you copy this company to the production
environment as new company CVR number
will not be copied so this new copied uh
company can be deleted until you enter
new CVR
number that's it about uh what is
updated because this is mostly not what
is new what is updated I want to share
with you these two links a compliance
explanation this is on our uh learning
page you can find uh article by article
from um DBA and how we comply with all
of them and you can find on new every
specific terms here on the second link
so you can find uh everything about Leal
perspective and then we have officially
a registered number VBA fob 46
7715 and you can find these documents in
this compliance explanation on our docs
page as
well um yes I want to encourage you to
watch all sessions but these two
sessions will be important for you
because now you will be en forced to use
e documents so uh I I definitely I think
it' be good idea to look what is new in
E documents I didn't talk too much about
e documents in this session because we
have independent session about e
documents and we have one really great
automation great example of using
co-pilot so you can watch introducing e
invoicing matching with co-pilot this is
in purchase process so you can automate
matching your purchase order with
incoming electronic
documents um please use some of these
resources bcam we are open there for
communication just to remind you we had
all the time open Denny bookkeeping EG
channel for direct communication about
that and we are trying to be transparent
of all other functionality what where we
are doing so you can directly
communicate with produ group AK msbc uh
Yammer we can communicate on on Twitter
or X join our BC office hours and all
your ideas please submit to BC ideas
this is the best way how you can uh get
more people who think the same as you
who will vote for this idea and this is
the the best sign we need to improve
something in a busy Central or to add
maybe some missing feature if you cannot
remember all of these things uh use akm
Ms BC all so all these links can find
there and one important because this is
local feature use AK msbc alerts every
time when you see the some new upcoming
regulatory requirements uh will show in
your country let us know in advance
because we cannot track all of them be
trying but sometimes maybe some of
important uh new regulatory things will
miss and let us know even if you have 10
times the same requirement this is much
better than not to get this regulatory
requirement at all and uh join us on Q&A
session both Arthur and I will be there
so we will try to probably to clarify
maybe this is still something is not
clear enough so we will try to clarify
to answer on your questions please join
us there and thank you for watching the
session